### **RESUME**

### **CHETHAN KUMAR.S**

Email ID : chethangowdasudesh@gmail.com.

Contact No: 9790650851,6383527954.

### **CAREER OBJECTIVE:**

To improve my skills and to be an asset to the organization and to succeed in all my endeavors, and to establish a successful career, rendering the best of my efforts with utmost sincerity and devotion.

# **Personal Strength:**

- \* Confident, Hard work and Discipline.
- \* Ability to handle any type of situations.
- \* Can easily work in a group.

# **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:**

S. No.	Qualification	Institution	Duration of Years
1	State board	Government	2009-2011
		Higher Secondary	
		School, Madhagondapalli.	
2	HSC	Government Higher Secondary School, Belagondapalli.	2011-2013
3	DMLT	Vivekanandha Institute of paramedical sciences,Lakshmipuram	2013-2015
4	Bsc.MLT	Yashwantrao Chavan Maharashtra Open University	2015-2018

#### SOFTWARE PROFICIENCY

Operating system : Windows XP-7 Computer Languages : Microsoft Office.

### Work experience details

Organization name: ANAND DIAGNOSTICS (A NEUBERG ASSOCIATE)-Kauvery

hospital,Konappana agrahara,Electronic city

**ROLE: TEAM LEADER (Technologist Grade II)** 

**Employment duration**: 20-Aug-2020- Present.

## <u>Job Responsibilities</u>

Perform equipment maintenance as per the defined schedule.

Perform analysis of internal quality control samples on each day of sample analysis and take corrective actions as and when required.

Receive samples in the LIS and check them for acceptability.

Analyse samples as with-in a time frame to enable release of reports with-in agreed upon TAT. Label all reagents and equipment and keep them updated.

Analyse EQAS samples with-in time lines, as and when assigned.

Record temperature of refrigerators and laboratory environmental conditions (temperature and humidity) in the defined formats.

Maintain record of all outsourced samples and the reports received.

Record the results in the raw data work sheets, where applicable and upload the completed results in LIS.

Inform all malfunctions (LIS/equipment) to relevant persons so that they are resolved as soon as possible.

**Preparing Duty roster.** 

Preparing sop's.

**Document controlling.** 

Registers and records maintaining.

Maintaining quality work as per organization protocol.

### **Work experience details**

<u>Organization name</u>: Care.fit Medical and Diagnostic Center -HSR Layout (NABL accredited), Bangalore.

**ROLE: SENIOR LAB TECHNICIAN** 

Employment duration: 08-Aug-2019 - 14th-Aug-2020

## <u>**Iob Responsibilities**</u>

Perform equipment maintenance as per the defined schedule.

Perform analysis of internal quality control samples on each day of sample analysis and take corrective actions as and when required.

Receive samples in the LIS and check them for acceptability.

Analyse samples as with-in a time frame to enable release of reports with-in agreed upon TAT. Label all reagents and equipment and keep them updated.

Analyse EQAS samples with-in time lines, as and when assigned.

Record temperature of refrigerators and laboratory environmental conditions (temperature and humidity) in the defined formats.

Maintain record of all outsourced samples and the reports received.

Record the results in the raw data work sheets, where applicable and upload the completed results in LIS.

Inform all malfunctions (LIS/equipment) to relevant persons so that they are resolved as soon as possible.

### **Previous work Experience:**

<u>Organization name</u>: MEDALL Health care & Diagnostics pvt.ltd at GUNAM MULTI SPECIALITY HOSPITAL, (NABH accredited).

**ROLE: SENIOR LAB TECHNICIAN** 

**Employment duration:** from June 2015-06-Aug-2019

**Job responsibilities:** 

**Document Management** 

**Night duty Incharge** 

**Indent Management** 

**Duty roster** 

**Analysis of IQC and EQAS samples** 

**Preparing Health Packages.** 

Sample analysis in Biochemistry, Hematology, Immunoassay, Clinical Pathology, Microbiology

Management of outsourced samples

Sample collection

Organization name: VMA Diagnostics, Hosur

Employment duration: from 15 Jan 2015-June 2015

## Job responsibilities:

Sample collection and Processing.

**Outsourcing Samples** 

**Maintaining TAT and STAT** 

Maintaining Documents and registers.

### **PERSONAL PROFILE**:

Name : CHETHAN KUMAR.S

Father's Name : SUDESH.K

Date of Birth : 25/04/1996

Age : 25 Yrs.

Sex : Male

Marital Status : Single.

**Languages Known** 

To speak & write : Tamil ,English,Telugu & Kannada.

Permanent Address : CHETHANKUMAR.S

No: 2/62, Ubbarayana pally (vill),

Denkanikottai (Taluk),

Krishnagiri (dist)

Mobile No. : 9790650851,6383527954.

Email ID : <a href="mailto:chethangowdasudesh@gmail.com">chethangowdasudesh@gmail.com</a>

Hobbies : Watching Movies, listening Music & Reading books

#### **DECLARATION:**

I hereby declare that the above furnished details are true to the best of

My knowledge and belief.

Place:

Date: Yours Truly,

(S.CHETHAN KUMAR)

<sup>\*</sup> Irish ions - Electrolytes analyzer.